{
    "subject": "resource/Sergey_Vasilyevich_Gerasimov",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Soviet_painters",
    "human_readable": "Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov is a subject of the category Soviet painters.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9576705694198608,
            "question": "Was Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov a painter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8679675459861755,
            "question": "What artistic field is associated with Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8632795214653015,
            "question": "To what category does Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.804515540599823,
            "question": "What were the characteristics of Soviet painting during Gerasimov's era?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7751665115356445,
            "question": "What nationality was Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7642000317573547,
            "question": "Are there any famous artworks by Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6218604445457458,
            "question": "What time period was Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov active in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48935502767562866,
            "question": "Can you name any famous Soviet painters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46830904483795166,
            "question": "Who are some other prominent figures in Soviet art history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2554604411125183,
            "question": "How did Soviet art reflect its political ideology?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov is a subject of the category Soviet painters.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1374_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other prominent figures in Soviet art history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1374_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any famous Soviet painters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1374_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What time period was Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov active in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1374_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1374_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1374_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1374_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1374_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1374_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1374_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1374_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1374_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1374_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1374_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov was a Soviet and Russian painter, and that he worked in the style of Socialist realism. This indicates that he is indeed a subject of the category Soviet painters."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide extensive information about Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov, including his role as a Soviet and Russian painter, his contributions to socialist realism, and his status as an academician and teacher. This information strongly supports the categorization of Sergey Vasilyevich Gerasimov under the category of \"Soviet painters.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}